5hippos.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy

Loading...

5hippos.com understands how important the privacy of personal information is to our users. We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy will tell you what information we collect about you and about your use of 5hippos and its services. 

Personal Information: 

If we will request personal information in the future when you register as a member of this site, we will ask you to supply an accurate email address and to specify your geographical location. You may chose, however, to hide your email address from the public, in which case it is held in the strictest of confidence. Your location does not have to be specific for example. You make the decision whether to proceed with any activity that   
requests personal information. 

Cookies: 

When you register as a member of 5hippos our web server will send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies do not damage your system. We will use cookies to recognize you when you are logged into the site. 

IP Address: 

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer's IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any web site within the 5hippos network, our web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. We will use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of the MyFreePlayYard Ltd network. 

Email Privacy: 

5hippos will use in the future subscription forms for individuals to request information by subscribing to email newsletters and/or email alerts based on their categories of interest. We collect contact information (like your name) to provide you with the information that you requested. We will not sell or rent email addresses to any 3rd parties. 

Children: 

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. Neither 5hippos nor any of its services are designed or intended to attract children under the age of 13. We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13. 

THIRD PARTY VENDORS: 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. One of these vendors is Google.   
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.   
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy. If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us: [Contact us form](http://www.5hippos.com/pages/contact-us)
